Preliminary Inventory to the Fly Papers on Squatters' Rights TAM.363
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Fly Papers on Squatters' Rights
1980s-2000s
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Fly.
TAM.363
0.5 Linear Feet (1 box)
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials donated by Fly in circa 2006. The accession number associated with this gift is 2006.022.
Historical/Biographical Note
Fly is a visual artist who was involved in the 1980s squatters' rights movement in New York City's East Village which culminated in the Tompkins Square Park Police Riot of August 1988.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of photographs, a scrapbook that contains clippings, artwork and photographs, and copies of zines, including Dog Days and Slug and Lettuce.
Squatters -- New York (State) -- New York; Lower East Side (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions.; Tompkins Square Park Riot, New York, N.Y., 1988.; Lower East Side (New York, N.Y.); Fly.
- Art Publications: Includes Dog Days and Peoples, 1990s-2000s; 285525 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Artworks, Photos, 1990s-2000s; 285526 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Clippings, 1990s-2000s; 285527 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Fliers, Leaflets, 1990s-2000s; 285529 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- "Inside Out: The Art World of the Squats" Exhibition Catalogue, 1990s-2000s; 285528 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Poster (framed), 1990s-2000s; 285530 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Posters, 1990s-2000s; 285531 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Slug and Lettuce numbers 39--57, 1990s-2000s; 285532 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Slug and Lettuce numbers 62--74, 1990s-2000s; 285533 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Slug and Lettuce numbers 79--85, 1990s-2000s; 285534; 0.5 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 10)